Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Public Relations records, 1934-1999 and undated RL.11700
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. Public Relations records
1934-1999 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company
RL.11700
45.0 Linear Feet
Founded in 1864, the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) is one of the oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies in the United States. It is headquartered in New York. Collection combines the public relations, publicity and promotional efforts of a number of JWT entities, including the Public Relations Department, Public Relations Division, Corporate Communications, Publicity Department, Personality Department and others. Collection includes news and press releases, clippings, photographs, scripts, directories, advertising proofs, print advertisements and other printed materials. Activities represented include baking and other contests, merchandising, nutritional campaigns, syndicated television programming, and youth outreach programs. Companies and institutions represented include 4-H clubs, American Gas Association, Bristol Myers, Burger King, Clairol, Ford, Kodak, Kraft, National Shoe Institute, Planters Peanuts, Radio City Music Hall, Reader's Digest, Royal Baking Powder, Scott Paper, Standard Brands, U.S. Brewer's Association and Warner-Lambert. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Arrangement
Organized into the following series: General Files; Accounts and New Business; Events and Activities; Organizations, Offices, Subsidiaries; and Staff.
Biographical / Historical
Founded in 1864, the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) is one of the oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies in the United States. It is headquartered in New York.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The J. Walter Thompson Company. Public Relations records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 1987-2000.
Related Materials
Related materials may be found in the following Hartman Center collections:
J. Walter Thompson Company. Account Files
J. Walter Thompson Company. Bill Lane papers
J. Walter Thompson Company. Brouillard Communications records
J. Walter Thompson Company. Lucile Turnbach Platt papers
J. Walter Thompson Company. Review Board records
J. Walter Thompson Company. Shirley F. Woodell papers
Nicole Di Bona Peterson collection of advertising cookbooks
Collection Overview
Collection combines the public relations, publicity and promotional efforts of a number of JWT entities, including the Public Relations Department, Public Relations Division, Corporate Communications, Publicity Department, Personality Department and others. Collection includes news and press releases, clippings, photographs, scripts, directories, advertising proofs, print advertisements and other printed materials. Activities represented include baking and other contests, merchandising, nutritional campaigns, syndicated television programming, and youth outreach programs. Companies and institutions represented include 4-H clubs, American Gas Association, Bristol Myers, Burger King, Clairol, Ford, Kodak, Kraft, National Shoe Institute, Planters Peanuts, Radio City Music Hall, Reader's Digest, Royal Baking Powder, Scott Paper, Standard Brands, U.S. Brewer's Association and Warner-Lambert. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Advertising; Advertising -- History; Advertising agencies; Advertising agencies -- United States; Advertising agencies -- United States -- History; Public relations; Publicity -- History -- 20th century; Press releases; Bristol-Myers Company; Burger King Corporation; Clairol, inc.; Ford Motor Company; Eastman Kodak Company; Kraft Foods Company; Reader's Digest Association; Scott Paper Company; Standard Brands Incorporated; Warner-Lambert Company; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
- General Files, 1934-1999 and undated; 1
  - :15 Commercials, 1985 (Box 1)
  - 100 Best TV Commercials, 1976 (Box 1)
  - AAAA (American Association of Advertising Agencies)--What Advertising Agencies Are, 1976 (Box 1)
  - AAF (American Advertising Federation)--Addy Awards, 1982-1988; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - AAF (American Advertising Federation)--Hall of Fame, 1976-1979 (Box 1)
  - Ad display, 11th floor, 1975 (Box 1)
  - Advertiser's Pocket Guide to Cable Communications, 1981-1986; 4 folders (Box 1)
  - Advertising Age--1990 Billings, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Advertising Age--Agency Audit, 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Advertising Age--Agency Income Reports, 1974-1986; 4 folders (Box 1)
  - Advertising Age--Agency Report, 1997-1998 (Box 1)
  - Advertising Age--International Agency Survey, 1984-1988 (Box 1)
  - Advertising Age--Jim O'Gara radio transcripts, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Advertising Age--JWT 125th anniversary, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Advertising Age--Special Reports, 1984 (Box 1)
  - Advertising Age--Summaries, 1974-1979; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Advertising Age--U.S. Employment, 1987-1991 (Box 1)
  - Advertising Age--Year-End Report, 1988-1991; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Advertising Career Opportunity in Media Planning, undated (Box 1)
  - Advertising economics articles, 1967-1985 (Box 1)
  - Advertorials and Infomercials, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Adweek--Agency Report Card, 1984-1987; 4 folders (Box 1)
  - Adweek--Databank survey, 1986 (Box 1)
  - Adweek--Directory, 1976-1987; 5 folders (Box 1)
  - American Consumer 1970-1990: Great Expectations, 1978 (Box 1)
  - American Consumer Myth and Reality, 1977 (Box 1)
  - Amerika TV miniseries, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Annual report materials, 1977 (Box 1)
  - Awards, 1984-1988 (Box 1)
  - Ban the Bullet campaign (handgun control), 1975 (Box 1)
  - Black Monday study, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Brand loyalty, 1977 (Box 1)
  - Caples Award (Direct response), 1987 (Box 1)
  - CEBA Awards (Communications Excellence to Black Audiences), 1986 (Box 1)
  - Changes in the Marketplace, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Cities in School program, 1975-1976 (Box 1)
  - Clean air memo, 1977 (Box 1)
  - Client confidentiality project, 1984 (Box 1)
  - Clilpping book, 1979-1982; 5 folders (Box 2)
  - Clipping file, 1981-1982; 6 folders (Box 2)
  - Clipping file--Awards and presentations, 1982 (Box 2)
  - Clipping file--Cable, 1982 (Box 2)
  - Clipping file--Financial, 1982 (Box 2)
  - Clipping file--International, 1982 (Box 2)
  - Clipping file--Media, 1979-1982; 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Clipping file--Research, 1982 (Box 2)
  - "Close-Up" meeting, 1975 (Box 2)
  - Commercial zapping, 1984-1985; 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Communications Department budget, 1982-1983 (Box 2)
  - Communications plan, 1982-1983; 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Communications program, 1976-1977; 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Communications program review, 1975 (Box 3)
  - Communications review, 1974-1982; 4 folders (Box 3)
  - Communications strategy plan, 1981 (Box 3)
  - Competitive agency comparisons, 1981 (Box 3)
  - Corporate communications, 1978-1979 (Box 3)
  - Corporate Communications 1991 Operational Plan, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Corporate communications budget, 1995-1997 (Box 3)
  - Corporate communications proposal, 1972 (Box 3)
  - Corporate communications recommendations, 1974 (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, 1976-1994; 3 folders (Box 3)
  - Creative awards book mailing, 1985 (Box 3)
  - Creative awards letters and mailing lists, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Developmental Research at JWT, 1978 (Box 3)
  - Director's Report on Coverage of Events, 1987 (Box 3)
  - Directory information, 1975 (Box 3)
  - Electronic Media Hotline, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Eyes on Thompson, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Eyes on Thompson memos, 1975 (Box 3)
  - Film--People Like Charlie, 1976 (Box 3)
  - Financial, 1975-1977 (Box 3)
  - Flippers: Changes in the Way Americans Watch TV, 1986 (Box 3)
  - Flippers/Zappers, 1985-1986 (Box 3)
  - Form 10-K (report to SEC), 1974 (Box 3)
  - Fortune articles on JWT, 1947-1979 (Box 3)
  - Freddie Mac ad mailing (Salute to the Commodore), 1985 (Box 3)
  - Gallagher Report, 1984 (Box 3)
  - Guidelines for the Use and Selection of Celebrities in Advertising, 1978 (Box 3)
  - Harvey Mandlin--The Making of a Television Commercial, 1974-1979 (Box 3)
  - History of Public Relations at JWT, undated (Box 3)
  - How Much Do Remote Control Devices Increase Flipping (TV), 1987 (Box 3)
  - "I didn't know J. Walter did that" mailing, 1985 (Box 3)
  - Impact of Network Revenues on TV Advertising, 1987 (Box 3)
  - In the News (Highlights), 1995-1999; 11 folders (Box 3)
  - Internal and External Communications 1976 Recommended Plan, 1975 (Box 3)
  - J. Walter Response campaign, 1983-1984 (Box 4)
  - JWT Agency of the Year, 1983 (Box 4)
  - JWT Awareness/Flighting model, 1985 (Box 4)
  - JWT billings, 1990 (Box 4)
  - JWT cable program research, 1982 (Box 4)
  - JWT communications program, 1975 (Box 4)
  - JWT Company Fund, undated (Box 4)
  - JWT corporate advertising, 1973 (Box 4)
  - JWT corporate objectives, 1981 (Box 4)
  - JWT Creative Library, 1985 (Box 4)
  - JWT financial news releases, 1973 (Box 4)
  - JWT formal reporting requirements, 1982 (Box 4)
  - JWT history materials, 1934-1987 and undated; 10 folders (Box 4)
  - JWT history materials, 1958-1977; 2 folders (Box 35)
  - JWT house campaign, 1991-1992 (Box 4)
  - JWT interactive/Internet, 1994-1996; 2 folders (Box 4)
  - JWT international news releases, 1973-1975 (Box 4)
  - JWT management succession, 1986; 3 folders (Box 4)
  - JWT miscellaneous information, 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - JWT PR video, 1992-1993 (Box 4)
  - JWT Target Planning Study, 1981 (Box 4)
  - JWT traveling archives, 1993 (Box 4)
  - JWT/USA awards information sheet, undated (Box 4)
  - JWT/USA creative awards memos and mailing lists, 1984 (Box 4)
  - JWT/USA speaker request form, undated (Box 4)
  - JWT/USA staff questionnaire, undated (Box 4)
  - Leadership at JWT, undated (Box 4)
  - Lists of addresses, undated (Box 4)
  - Madison Avenue Magazine, 1974-1975 (Box 4)
  - Managers' Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - Marketing Information in Transition: Scanner Services and Single Source Systems, 1987 (Box 4)
  - Media Department management, 1975 (Box 4)
  - Media forecast, 1974 (Box 4)
  - Media Interchange Hotline, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Media relations program, 1975 (Box 4)
  - Media relations radio, 1975 (Box 4)
  - Media spending, 1985-1988 (Box 4)
  - Memos, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Memos--Desk to desk, 1987 (Box 4)
  - Memos--Don Johnston, to clients regarding management changes, 1987; 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Memos--JWT/USA all-staff, 1982-1987; 3 folders (Box 5)
  - Memos--Linda Tomlinson, 1983-1984; 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Memos--New York staff, 1974 (Box 5)
  - Memos--Reorganization, 1973-1977 (Box 5)
  - Memos--Thomas Robbins, 1984-1987; 14 folders (Box 5)
  - Menscope, 1986 (Box 5)
  - Merchandising, 1974-1979; 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Merchandising scrapbook--Contests, 1947-1949 (Box 37)
  - Merchandising scrapbook--Contests, 1950-1952 (Box 38)
  - Merchandising scrapbook--Contests, 1953-1954 (Box 39)
  - Merchandising scrapbook--Coupons, 1952 (Box 40)
  - Merchandising scrapbook--Coupons, 1953-1954 (Box 41)
  - Merchandising scrapbook--Premiums--Adults, 1947-1949 (Box 42)
  - Merchandising scrapbook--Premiums--Adults, 1950-1951 (Box 43)
  - Merchandising scrapbook--Premiums--Adults, 1952 (Box 44)
  - Merchandising scrapbook--Premiums--Adults, 1952-1954 (Box 45)
  - Merchandising scrapbook--Premiums--Children, 1947-1950 (Box 46)
  - Merchandising scrapbook--Premiums--Children, 1951-1954 (Box 47)
  - Merchandising scrapbook--Promotional deals, 1947-1950 (Box 48)
  - Merchandising scrapbook--Promotional deals, 1950-1951 (Box 49)
  - Merchandising scrapbook--Promotional deals, 1952 (Box 50)
  - Mergers and conflicts, 1986-1987 (Box 5)
  - Metrication, 1975 (Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous, 1973-1986; 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous, 1985-1994; 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Myth and Reality, 1978 (Box 6)
  - Network TV costs, ratings, share trends, 1985 (Box 6)
  - New American Consumers, 1985-1986 and undated; 5 folders (Box 6)
  - New Media Explorers, 1981; 2 folders (Box 6)
  - New Research Services, 1975 (Box 6)
  - New TV Center at JWT, 1975 (Box 6)
  - News releases, 1974-1987; 4 folders (Box 6)
  - NYA Business Development, 1975 (Box 6)
  - People Magazine--Experts'Guide to the Baby Boomers, 1985 (Box 6)
  - Personality Department scrapbook--Lucille Platt book of sample testimonial ads, 1955-1956 (Box 51)
  - Personality Department scrapbook--Typical proofs samples, 1960 (Box 52)
  - Pocket Guide to Media Terms and Media Math, 1984 (Box 6)
  - PR Special Projects Activities Reports, 1984-1988; 23 folders (Box 34)
  - Press and photographs of sponsored television shows (includes Speakeasy with Chip Monck), 1974 (Box 6)
  - Press contacts, 1985-1986 (Box 6)
  - Press releases, 1973-1981; 7 folders (Box 6)
  - Primetime Soap Trends 1980-1984, 1985 (Box 6)
  - Product Life Cycle, 1976 (Box 6)
  - Public Relations Review, 1978 (Box 6)
  - Recent Trends in Couponing, 1987; 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Red Book listings, 1984-1986 (Box 6)
  - Reference file, 1983-1985 (Box 6)
  - Research--Black consumer market, 1974; 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Research--Do America's Junior Misses Watch MTV?, 1984 (Box 6)
  - Research--JWT Target Study, 1975 (Box 6)
  - Research--Magazines, undated (Box 7)
  - Research--Spanish language market, 1974 (Box 7)
  - Research--Target Group Index (TGI), 1976 (Box 7)
  - Research--Working and non-working women, 1974 (Box 7)
  - Retail displays (Gimbel's, FAO Schwarz, B. Altman), 1980 (Box 7)
  - Satellite Communications of Spot Media Buying Data (WESTAR), 1975 (Box 7)
  - Split :30 commercials, 1984-1985 (Box 7)
  - SRI tracking study, 1988-1989 (Box 7)
  - Super Bowl XIX and the Million-Dollar Minute, 1985 (Box 7)
  - Survey of business/financial editors, 1977 (Box 7)
  - Talking to Women, 1991 (Box 7)
  - Telecommunications, 1975-1979; 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Television Season II: 1975-1976 (Box 7)
  - The Ascent of Woman, 1991 (Box 7)
  - The Big Idea (DeBeers Japan, Haagen-Dazs), 1995 (Box 7)
  - The Big Picture video magazine, 1994; 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Thompson Achievement Awards program, 1983 (Box 7)
  - Top 10 U.S. Agencies, 1975 (Box 7)
  - Top Executives' media habits study, 1987 (Box 7)
  - TV Viewer Attitudes Toward Commercials, 1981-1985 (Box 7)
  - TV Violence: In the Eyes of the Beholders, 1977 (Box 7)
  - Video storyboard tests, 1983-1987 (Box 7)
  - What JWT Stands For, undated (Box 7)
  - What Women Want, 1995 (Box 7)
  - Why JWT Is Bullish on Cable, 1981 (Box 7)
  - William Cameron--Statement for Media Professionals, 1975 (Box 7)
  - Winter Olympics, 1984 (Box 7)
  - Womenscope, 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Worldwide case study, 1994-1995 (Box 7)
  - Worldwide PR Council, 1994-1995 (Box 7)
  - Write If You Want Work campaign, 1989-1992; 3 folders (Box 7)
- Accounts and New Business, 1949-1997 and undated; 2
  - Account gains and losses, 1982-1985; 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Account management organization, 1985 (Box 7)
  - Accounts resigned or lost, 1960-1983 (Box 7)
  - Acme Supermarkets, 1987 (Box 7)
  - Activision, 1984 (Box 7)
  - Advisory Council for Jams, Jellies and Preserves--Recipes and mailings, undated (Box 7)
  - AFSCME (American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees), 1977 (Box 7)
  - Allegheny Airlines, 1976-1977 (Box 7)
  - American Cancer Society, 1974 (Box 7)
  - American Chicle, 1974 (Box 7)
  - American Gas Association, 1973-1976 (Box 7)
  - American Gas Association--Alice Through the Looking Glass, 1966; 3 folders (Box 7)
  - American Gas Association--Androcles and the Lion, 1967 (Box 7)
  - American Gas Association--Annie Get Your Gun, 1966-1967 (Box 7)
  - American Gas Association--Call reports, 1966; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - American Gas Association--Christmas with Lorne Greene, 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - American Gas Association--Commercials, 1966-1967 (Box 8)
  - American Gas Association--Executive conference, 1966 (Box 8)
  - American Gas Association--Jack and the Beanstalk, 1967; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - American Gas Association--Julie Andrews Show, 1965-1968; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - American Gas Association--Legend of Robin Hood, 1967-1968 (Box 8)
  - American Gas Association--Mary Martin, 1966 (Box 8)
  - American Gas Association--Memos, 1966-1967 (Box 8)
  - American Gas Association--Norval Jennings correspondence, 1965-1966; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - American Gas Association--Samples of promotions, 1967-1968 (Box 8)
  - American Gas Association--Specials, 1965-1967 (Box 8)
  - American Gas Association--Television budgets, 1964 (Box 8)
  - American Gas Association--The American Image, 1966-1967 (Box 8)
  - American Gas Association--The Law and the Prophets, 1965-1967; 3 folders (Box 8)
  - American Gas Association--The Royal Palaces, 1966-1967 (Box 8)
  - American Postal Workers Union, 1982 (Box 8)
  - American Red Cross, 1975-1988; 4 folders (Box 8)
  - Anniversary memos, 1915-1977 (Box 8)
  - Apple case study, 1984 (Box 8)
  - Audio Devices (Capitol Music Tapes), 1974 (Box 8)
  - B. Altman, 1979 (Box 8)
  - Baby Fresh, 1985-1986 (Box 8)
  - Backstage Forum, 1977 (Box 8)
  - Bali Blinds, 1984 (Box 8)
  - Bausch & Lomb, 1975 (Box 8)
  - Beatrice, 1975 (Box 8)
  - Bell South, 1988 (Box 8)
  - Benetton, 1990-1991 (Box 8)
  - Big Apple Circus, 1977 (Box 8)
  - Big Key Self Storage, 1994 (Box 8)
  - Blue Cross/Blue Shield, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Bob Hope Heart Research Institute, 1982 (Box 8)
  - Bristol-Myers, 1992-1996 (Box 9)
  - Bristol-Myers--Excedrin, 1993 (Box 9)
  - Bristol-Myers--Nuprin, 1991-1994; 3 folders (Box 9)
  - Bristol-Myers--Theragran, 1992-1994 (Box 9)
  - Burger King, 1976-1987; 3 folders (Box 9)
  - Burger King--Original Burger King character, 1977 (Box 9)
  - Burger King--Press coverage, 1985 (Box 35)
  - Burger King--Press coverage, 1987 (Box 36)
  - Burger King--Radio City Music Hall, 1980 (Box 9)
  - California Lottery, 1992-1993 (Box 9)
  - California Tourism, 1993-1994 (Box 9)
  - Calvin Klein--Jeans case study, 1985 (Box 9)
  - Calvin Klein--Obsession case study, 1985 (Box 9)
  - Chanel--#5 case study, 1985 (Box 9)
  - Changes in account status, 1984 (Box 9)
  - Chatham Supermarkets, 1974 (Box 9)
  - Chemical Manufacturer's Association, 1979 (Box 9)
  - Chesebrough-Pond's, 1987 (Box 9)
  - Chesebrough-Pond's--Fresh Start, 1964 (Box 9)
  - Chesebrough-Pond's--Study of PR Activities, 1960 (Box 9)
  - Chevron--"Yes" campaign, 1985 (Box 9)
  - Children Now, 1996 (Box 9)
  - Chrysler case study, 1984-1985 (Box 9)
  - City Harvest, 1986 (Box 9)
  - Clairol, 1992-1995 (Box 9)
  - Clairol--Linda Evangelista, 1995 (Box 9)
  - Clairol--Loving Care, 1992-1993 (Box 9)
  - Clairol--Nice 'N Easy, 1993-1995 (Box 9)
  - Clairol--Ultimate Blonde, 1991-1992 (Box 9)
  - Clairol--Ultress, 1994-1995 (Box 9)
  - Client lists, 1985; 3 folders (Box 9)
  - Clipping file, 1982-1985; 4 folders (Box 9)
  - Close-Up case study, 1985 (Box 9)
  - Committee to Save Grand Central Station, 1977-1978 (Box 9)
  - Concord Grape Association--Recipe mailing card, undated (Box 9)
  - Congoleum, 1975-1976; 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Coors, 1978-1984; 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Daewoo, 1984-1986 (Box 9)
  - DeBeers, 1995-1996 (Box 9)
  - DeBeers (in French), 1995 (Box 36)
  - Del Taco, 1992 (Box 9)
  - DeVilbiss, 1975 (Box 9)
  - Dior, 1982 (Box 9)
  - Eastman Chemical, 1975 (Box 9)
  - Eaton--American Parade, 1974 (Box 9)
  - Eckerd Drug, 1985 (Box 9)
  - Emery Worldwide, 1984-1986; 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Emery Worldwide--Case study, 1985 (Box 10)
  - Equitable Life Insurance, 1986 (Box 10)
  - Esso UK, 1991 (Box 10)
  - Federal Express, 1981-1982 (Box 10)
  - Florida Citrus Commission, 1974 (Box 10)
  - Food and Drug Administration--Nutrition labeling program, 1974 (Box 10)
  - Ford, 1974-1997; 5 folders (Box 10)
  - Ford--Articles, 1993-1995; 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Ford--Credit card, 1991-1993 (Box 10)
  - Ford--Escort, 1981-1986 (Box 10)
  - Ford--Escort (Brussels), 1980 (Box 10)
  - Ford--Granada, 1977-1985 (Box 10)
  - Ford--Japan, 1987 (Box 10)
  - Ford--JWT employee rebate, 1975 (Box 10)
  - Ford--Lowell Thomas Narrates Ford History, 1976 (Box 10)
  - Ford--Reassignment of small cars to JWT, 1975 (Box 10)
  - Ford/Jaguar, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Freddie Mac, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Galaxy Latin America (GLA), 1995 (Box 10)
  - Galway Crystal (Wedgwood), 1977 (Box 10)
  - General, 1979-1984 (Box 10)
  - General Electric--Information Services Business Division, 1973 (Box 10)
  - General Electric Credit Corporation (GECC), 1977-1978 (Box 10)
  - Georgia Department of Industry, Trade and Tourism, 1992-1993 (Box 10)
  - Gerber baby foods, 1992-1994 (Box 10)
  - Gift America, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
  - Gillette--Alberto Culver litigation, 1979 (Box 10)
  - Gillette--Athletes campaign, 1972 (Box 10)
  - Goodyear, 1990-1995 (Box 10)
  - Gorey Stories, 1978 (Box 10)
  - Gotham Bar and Grill, 1996 (Box 10)
  - Guerlain, 1985-1986 (Box 10)
  - Hewlett-Packard, 1984 (Box 10)
  - Holiday Inn, 1974-1975 (Box 10)
  - Houston Police, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Hyatt, 1985 (Box 10)
  - IBM, 1986 (Box 10)
  - IBM Canada, 1982 (Box 10)
  - International account gains and losses, 1986 (Box 10)
  - Irving Trust, 1975 (Box 10)
  - Johnston and Murphy shoes, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Jovan, undated (Box 10)
  - JWT/USA client contact list, 1984 (Box 10)
  - JWT/USA new business, 1984 (Box 10)
  - JWT/USA new client questionnaire (form), undated (Box 10)
  - Kellogg, 1992-1996 (Box 10)
  - Kellogg--All-Bran case study, 1986 (Box 10)
  - Kellogg--Raisin Bran, 1995 (Box 10)
  - Ken-L-Ration, 1985 (Box 10)
  - Kentucky Fried Chicken, 1988 (Box 10)
  - Kodak, 1973-1987; 5 folders (Box 10)
  - Kodak, 1984-1997; 4 folders (Box 11)
  - Kodak--Advantix (with Dennis Rodman), 1995-1996 (Box 11)
  - Kodak--Articles, 1990-1994 (Box 11)
  - Kodak--Daddy's Little Girl, 1990 (Box 11)
  - Kodak--For the Time of Your Life, 1973 (Box 11)
  - Kodak--Funsaver, 1994-1996 (Box 11)
  - Kodak--Gift promotion, 1959; 3 folders (Box 11)
  - Kodak--How-to articles, 1962 (Box 11)
  - Kodak--Korea, 1996 (Box 11)
  - Kodak--News from Kodak, 1978 (Box 11)
  - Kodak--News releases, 1977-1978; 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Kodak--Olympics, 1992-1996 (Box 11)
  - Kodak--Photo CD system, 1992 (Box 11)
  - Kodak--Royal Gold, 1994 (Box 11)
  - Kodak--Spinners, 1975 (Box 11)
  - Kodak--Tie-in promotions (Kodak content in advertisements for other products), 1957-1961; 8 folders (Box 11)
  - Kodak--Tie-in promotions (Kodak content in advertisements for other products), 1961-1963; 3 folders (Box 12)
  - Kodak--"Time of Your Life" song, 1975 (Box 35)
  - Kodak--United Kingdom, 1994 (Box 12)
  - Kraft, 1992-1995 (Box 12)
  - Kraft--Chronicles of Narnia, 1977 (Box 12)
  - Kraft--Kraft Television Specials, 1981 (Box 12)
  - Kraft--Lender's Bagels, 1993-1996 (Box 12)
  - Kraft--Miracle Whip, undated (Box 12)
  - Kraft--Singles, 1985 (Box 12)
  - Kraft--The Play of St. Nicholas (with Douglas Fairbanks), 1982 (Box 12)
  - Kraft--Velveeta, 1984 (Box 12)
  - Kuppenheimer, 1984 (Box 12)
  - Labatt's, 1977 (Box 12)
  - Les Halles, 1991 (Box 12)
  - Lone Star Industries, 1975 (Box 12)
  - Lykes-Youngstown, 1975 (Box 12)
  - Lyon's Restaurants, 1994 (Box 12)
  - Magazine Publishers Association--Freedom of Choice campaign, 1976 (Box 12)
  - Marine Corps, 1982-1996 and undated; 3 folders (Box 12)
  - Marine Corps--Sword campaign, 1984 (Box 12)
  - Maui County Visitors Association, 1974 (Box 12)
  - Miles Laboratories, 1975-1976 (Box 12)
  - Miller Brewing, 1984-1985; 4 folders (Box 12)
  - Miller Brewing, 1985 (Oversize-folder 1)
  - Mink International, 1975-1987; 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Motorola, 1992-1994 (Box 12)
  - Mott's, 1992-1995 (Box 12)
  - National Shoe Institute--Campus promotion, 1949; 2 folders (Box 12)
  - National Shoe Institute--Fact sheets (Strictly for the Girls, Lines for Listeners), 1949-1950 (Box 12)